<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chillja</title>
    <link>https://chillja.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on chillja</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 19:45:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chillja.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Armadillo #3 - Documenting and Measurements</title>
      <link>https://chillja.github.io/blog/project-armadillo-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 19:45:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillja.github.io/blog/project-armadillo-3/</guid>
      <description>This post is solely for documentation and will be updated continuously. It will hold pictures, measurements and bits of knowledge that I found on the way and would rather not forget.
Measurements on old French bicycles from the 70s (and before and after) can differ all over the bike from the standards that were around that time and today. You can find a lot of information on this in the infamous archives of Sheldon Brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Armadillo #2 - Researching Year and Model</title>
      <link>https://chillja.github.io/blog/project-armadillo-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 23:34:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillja.github.io/blog/project-armadillo-2/</guid>
      <description>After having introduced the project in the first post of this series, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to take you along my efforts to accurately identify the bike. The bike was handed to me 3rd hand without that information - and let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, who really remembers the detailed bike model and year of a bike you bought 40 years ago?1
There are a number of things we can go by:
 Decals Parts Accessories  Year After some aimless research2 on the internet I first came across an interesting post in a forum (web archive).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Armadillo #1 - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://chillja.github.io/blog/project-armadillo-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 17:40:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillja.github.io/blog/project-armadillo-1/</guid>
      <description>This is the first in a series of posts, where I intend to document my small restoration project: Project Armadillo.
Project Armadillo is a 70s Peugeot road bicycle which was handed to me by a friend in trust, who again had it from a friend who realised they didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time to enjoy it anymore. So it came into my hands after some years (I guess) of rest and therefore - and due to its age - needs some work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My personal website</title>
      <link>https://chillja.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 16:44:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillja.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>this website .. is still under construction. It shall remain static.
summary Interested in everything that makes digital things better, safer and less cumbersome. From instruction sets and operating systems to programming languages and development processes, from writing a single good line of code to solving NP-hard problems.
disclaimer This is my private website. Opinions expressed are my own and do not represent my employer. You can find my professional web representation here:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>